<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hosting on Sridhar quick notes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/hosting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hosting on Sridhar quick notes</description>
    <image>
      <title>Sridhar quick notes</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.145.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:20:35 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/hosting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Momentum Trading</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/momentum-trading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:20:35 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/momentum-trading/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At first glance, momentum investing appears more like a reflexive response to market trends than a deliberate investing strategy. The concept of selling underperforming assets and purchasing those on the rise is enticing, but it directly challenges the timeless Wall Street principle of &amp;ldquo;buy low, sell high.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article explores the concept of momentum investing, examining its advantages and drawbacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Richard Driehaus wasn&amp;rsquo;t the pioneer of momentum investing, he refined the approach and implemented it as the cornerstone of his fund management strategy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nginx Dot Net Core</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/nginxdotnetcore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 11:31:36 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/nginxdotnetcore/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-was-stock-filter-installed&#34;&gt;How was Stock filter installed?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stockfilter is a Dot Net application that uses the inbuilt webserver Kestrel to host the application. Kestrel is a light weight web server for hosting ASP.NET Core applications on really any platform. Kestrel lacks a lot of the things that an ASP.NET web developer might have come to expect from a web server like IIS. For instance you cannot do SSL termination with Kestrel or URL rewrites or GZip compression.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blazor on RP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/blazor-on-rp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 11:28:39 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/blazor-on-rp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have always been interested in creating a blog using Blazor, a web framework that allows me to write C# code for both the client and the server side. I also wanted to host it on a Raspberry Pi, a low-cost and portable device that can run Linux and .NET applications. In this post, I will share how I configured my Blazing Blog, the name I gave to my project, on my Raspberry Pi.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
